<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eula>
	<title>
		Facebook's Statement of Rights and Responsibilities
	</title>
	<lastupdate>
		November 15, 2013.
	</lastupdate>
	<pages>
		<page>
			<text>
			&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;This Statement of Rights and Responsibilities (&quot;Statement,&quot; &quot;Terms&quot;, or &quot;SRR&quot;) derives from the Facebook Principles, and is our terms of service that governs our relationship with users and others who interact with Facebook. By using or accessing Facebook, you agree to this Statement, as updated from time to time in accordance with Section 14 below. Additionally, you will find resources at the end of this document that help you understand how Facebook works.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;1. Privacy&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;Your privacy is very important to us. We designed our Data Use Policy to make important disclosures about how you can use Facebook to share with others and how we collect and can use your content and information.  We encourage you to read the Data Use Policy, and to use it to help you make informed decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;2. Sharing Your Content and Information&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt; You own all of the content and information you post on Facebook, and you can control how it is shared through your privacy and application settings. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;1. For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, like photos and videos (IP content), you specifically give us the following permission, subject to your privacy and application settings: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP content that you post on or in connection with Facebook (IP License). This IP License ends when you delete your IP content or your account unless your content has been shared with others, and they have not deleted it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;2. When you delete IP content, it is deleted in a manner similar to emptying the recycle bin on a computer. However, you understand that removed content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;3. When you use an application, the application may ask for your permission to access your content and information as well as content and information that others have shared with you.  We require applications to respect your privacy, and your agreement with that application will control how the application can use, store, and transfer that content and information.  (To learn more about Platform, including how you can control what information other people may share with applications, read our Data Use Policy and Platform Page.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;4. When you publish content or information using the Public setting, it means that you are allowing everyone, including people off of Facebook, to access and use that information, and to associate it with you (i.e., your name and profile picture).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;5. We always appreciate your feedback or other suggestions about Facebook, but you understand that we may use them without any obligation to compensate you for them (just as you have no obligation to offer them).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;3. Safety&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;We do our best to keep Facebook safe, but we cannot guarantee it. We need your help to keep Facebook safe, which includes the following commitments by you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;1. You will not post unauthorized commercial communications (such as spam) on Facebook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;2. You will not collect users&#39; content or information, or otherwise access Facebook, using automated means (such as harvesting bots, robots, spiders, or scrapers) without our prior permission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;3. You will not engage in unlawful multi-level marketing, such as a pyramid scheme, on Facebook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;4. You will not upload viruses or other malicious code.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;5. You will not solicit login information or access an account belonging to someone else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;6. You will not bully, intimidate, or harass any user.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;7. You will not post content that: is hate speech, threatening, or pornographic; incites violence; or contains nudity or graphic or gratuitous violence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;8. You will not develop or operate a third-party application containing alcohol-related, dating or other mature content (including advertisements) without appropriate age-based restrictions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;9. You will follow our Promotions Guidelines and all applicable laws if you publicize or offer any contest, giveaway, or sweepstakes (“promotion”) on Facebook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;10. You will not use Facebook to do anything unlawful, misleading, malicious, or discriminatory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;11. You will not do anything that could disable, overburden, or impair the proper working or appearance of Facebook, such as a denial of service attack or interference with page rendering or other Facebook functionality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;12. You will not facilitate or encourage any violations of this Statement or our policies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			</text>
		</page>
	</pages>
</eula>